[静音]
Expanding is the task of taking a shorter piece of text,
“扩展(expanding)”是指将较短的文本片段，
such as a set of instructions or a list of topics,
例如一组说明或主题列表，
and having the large language model generate a longer piece of text,
让大型语言模型生成更长的文本，
such as an email or an essay about some topic.
例如，有关某个主题的电子邮件或文章。
There are some great uses of this,
这有一些很好的用途，
such as if you use a large language model as a brainstorming partner.
例如，将大型语言模型当做一个进行头脑风暴的伙伴。
But I just also want to acknowledge that there's
但我还想承认这也存在一些
some problematic use cases of this,
问题用例
such as if someone were to use it to generate a large amount of spam.
例如某人将其用于生成大量垃圾邮件。
So when you use these capabilities of a large language model,
因此，当您使用大型语言模型的这些能力时，
please use it only in a responsible way and in a way that helps people.
请只在负责任的方式和有助于人们的方式下使用。
In this video, we'll go through an example of how you can use
在本视频中，我们将演示如何使用语言模型根据某些信息生成个性化的电子邮件。
a language model to generate a personalized email based on some information.
使用语言模型生成一封基于某些信息的个性化电子邮件。
The email is kind of self-proclaimed to be from an AI bot,
该电子邮件自称是来自一个AI机器人，
which as Andrew mentioned, is very important.
正如安德鲁所提到的那样，这非常重要。
We're also going to use another one of
我们还将使用模型的另一个
the model's input parameters called temperature,
输入参数，称为“temperature”(“随机性参数”),
and this allows you to vary the degree of
这允许您改变模型响应中的
exploration and variety in the model's responses.
可探索性和多样性程度。
So let's get into it.
因此，让我们开始吧。
So before we get started,
在我们开始之前，
we're going to do the usual setup.
我们将进行通常的设置。
So set up the OpenAI Python package,
设置OpenAI Python软件包，
and then also define our helper function, get_Completion.
然后还要定义我们的helper函数、get_Completion。
Now we're going to write a custom email response to a customer review.
现在，我们将撰写对客户评论制定邮件响应。
So given a customer review and the sentiment,
我们将使用语言模型生成一封针对客户评论和评论情感的电子邮件。
we're going to generate a custom response.
我们将生成一个定制响应。
Now we're going to use the language model to generate
现在，我们将使用语言模型生成一封针对客户评论和评论情感的电子邮件。
a custom email to a customer based on a customer review and the sentiment of the review.
基于客户评论和评论情感，生成一封面向客户的定制电子邮件。
So we've already extracted the sentiment
我们已经提取了情感，
using the kind of prompts that we saw in the inferring video,
使用我们在推断视频中看到的提示，
and then this is the customer review for a blender.
这是关于搅拌机的客户评论。
Now we're going to customize the reply based on the sentiment.
现在，我们将根据情感定制回复。
So here the instruction is,
在这里，指令是：
you are a customer service AI assistant.
您是客户服务AI助手。
Your task is to send an email reply to a valued customer.
您的任务是向重要客户发送电子邮件回复。
Given the customer email delimited by three backticks,
鉴于客户电子邮件由三个反引号分隔，
generate a reply to thank the customer for their review.
请生成一封回复以感谢客户的评论。
If the sentiment is positive or neutral,
如果情感是正面的或中性的，
thank them for their review.
感谢他们的评论。
If the sentiment is negative,
如果情感是负面的，
apologize and suggest that they can reach out to customer service.
道歉并建议他们可以联系客户服务。
Make sure to use specific details from the review,
确保使用评论中的具体细节，
write in a concise and professional tone,
用简洁和专业的语气写作，
and sign the email as AI customer agent.
并以AI客户代理的身份签署电子邮件。
When you're using a language model to
当您使用语言模型生成要向
generate text that you're going to show to a user,
您将要向用户展示的文本时，
it's very important to have this kind of transparency
非常重要的是要有这种透明性，
and let the user know that the text they're seeing was generated by AI.
让用户知道他们看到的文本是由AI生成的。
Then we'll just input the customer review and the review sentiment.
然后，我们只需输入客户评论和评论情感。
Also note that this part isn't necessarily important,
还要注意，这部分并不一定重要，
because we could actually use this prompt to also
因为我们实际上可以使用此提示来提取评论情感，然后在后续步骤中编写电子邮件。
extract the review sentiment and then in a follow-up step, write the email.
提取评论情感，然后在后续步骤中撰写电子邮件。
But just for the sake of the example,
但是为了这个例子，
well, we've already extracted the sentiment from the review.
我们已经从评论中提取了情感。
So here we have a response to the customer.
因此，我们对客户做出了回应。
It addresses details that the customer mentioned in their review.
它解决了客户在评论中提到的细节问题。
As we instructed,
正如我们的指示，
suggest that they reach out to customer service because
建议他们联系客户服务，因为
that this is just an AI customer service agent.
这仅仅是一个AI客服代理。
Next, we're going to use a parameter of the language model called temperature
接下来，我们将使用语言模型的一个参数，叫做temperature（以下翻译成：“随机性参数”）
that will allow us to change the variety of the model's responses.
这个参数可以改变模型生成响应时的多样性。
So you can think of temperature as
你可以将“随机性参数”视为
the degree of exploration or randomness of the model.
模型探索或随机性的程度。
So for this particular phrase,
例如，在这个短语中：
my favorite food is,
“我最喜欢的食物是”
the most likely next word that the model predicts is pizza,
模型预测的最有可能的下一个单词是pizza，
and the next two most likely,
其次最有可能的是sushi和tacos。
So at a temperature of zero,
当“随机性参数”为0时，
the model will always choose the most likely next word,
模型总是选择最有可能的下一个单词，即pizza。
At a higher temperature,
当“随机性参数”较高时，
it will also choose one of the less likely words,
模型还会选择其中一个不太可能的单词，
and at an even higher temperature,
在更高的“随机性参数”下，
it might even choose tacos,
可能会选择tacos，
which only has a five percent chance of being chosen.
这种情况只有5％的概率被选择。
You can imagine that as the model continues this final response,
可以想象，当模型继续生成最终响应时，
so my favorite food is pizza,
“所以我的最爱是比萨饼，”
and it continues to generate more words,
“并且它继续生成更多单词，”
this response will diverge from the first response,
“此响应将与第一个响应分歧，”
which is my favorite food is tacos.
“也就是我的最爱是tacos。”
So as the model continues,
因此，随着模型的继续，
these two responses will become more and more different.
这两个响应将变得越来越不同。
In general, when building applications where you want
一般来说，当构建需要
a predictable response,
可预测的响应的应用程序时，
I would recommend using temperature zero.
建议使用“随机性参数”为0。
Throughout all of these videos,
在这些视频中，
we've been using temperature zero,
我们一直使用的是“随机性参数”为0，
and I think that if you're trying to build a system that is reliable,
我认为，如果你想要构建一个可靠的系统，
and predictable, you should go with this.
而且可预测的话，应该使用这个方法。
If you're trying to use the model in a more creative way,
如果你想以更有创造性的方式使用模型，
where you might want a wider variety of different outputs,
那么你可能想要获得更多不同的输出，
you might want to use a higher temperature.
这时你可能需要使用更高的“随机性参数”。
So now let's take this same prompt that we just used,
现在，让我们使用刚刚使用过的相同提示，
and let's try generating an email,
并尝试生成一封电子邮件，
but let's use a higher temperature.
但这次使用一个更高的“随机性参数”。
So in our getCompletion function that we've been using throughout the videos,
因此，在我们一直在视频中使用的getCompletion函数中，
we have specified a model and then also a temperature,
我们已经指定了一个模型和一个“随机性参数”，
but we've set them to default.
但是我们将它们设置为默认值。
So now let's try varying the temperature.
所以现在让我们尝试改变“随机性参数”。
So we use the prompt,
我们使用提示，
and then let's try temperature 0.7.
然后尝试使用“随机性参数”=0.7。
And so with temperature zero,
所以在“随机性参数”为0的情况下，
every time you execute the same prompt,
每次执行相同的提示时，
you should expect the same completion,
你应该期望得到相同的完成结果，
whereas with temperature 0.7,
而使用“随机性参数”=0.7，
you'll get a different output every time.
你会每次得到不同的输出。
So here we have our email,
因此，这里是我们的电子邮件，
and as you can see, it's different to the email
正如你所看到的，它与之前收到的电子邮件不同。
that we kind of received previously.
之前收到的那个。
And let's just execute it again
现在，让我们再次执行它，
to show that we'll get a different email again.
以证明我们会再次得到一个不同的电子邮件。
And here we have another different email.
这里是另一个不同的电子邮件。
So I recommend that you kind of play around with temperature yourself.
因此，我建议您自己试试“随机性参数”。
Maybe you could pause the video now and try this prompt
也许您现在可以暂停视频，尝试这个提示，
with a variety of different temperatures,
使用各种不同的“随机性参数”，
just to see how the outputs vary.
只是为了看看输出如何变化。
So to summarize, at higher temperatures，
因此，总的来说，在更高的“随机性参数”下，
the outputs from the model are kind of more random.
模型的输出更加随机。
You can almost think of it as that at higher temperatures,
您可以将其想象成在更高的“随机性参数”下，
the assistant is more distractible,
助手更容易分心，
but maybe more creative.
但也可能更有创造性。
In the next video,
在下一个视频中，
we're going to talk more about the chat completions endpoint format
我们将更多地讨论聊天完成终端点格式，
and how you can create a custom chatbot using this format.
以及如何使用此格式创建自定义聊天机器人。